// ============== Creating an array of questions and answers

let questions = [
    {
        number: 1,
        quesTime: 15,
        question: "Which type of JavaScript language is ___",
        answer: "Object-Based",
        options: ["Object-Oriented", "Object-Based", "Assembly-language", "High-level"],
    },
    {
        number: 2,
        quesTime: 15,
        question: " Which one of the following also known as Conditional Expression:",
        answer: "immediate if",
        options: [
            "Alternative to if-else",
            "Switch statement",
            "If-then-else statement",
            "immediate if"],
    },
    {
        number: 3,
        quesTime: 15,
        question: "In JavaScript, what is a block of statement?",
        answer: "block that combines a number of statements into a single compound statement",
        options: [
            "Conditional block",
            "block that combines a number of statements into a single compound statement",
            "both conditional block and a single statement",
            "block that contains a single statement"],
    },
    {
        number: 4,
        quesTime: 15,
        question: "When interpreter encounters an empty statements, what it will do:",
        answer: "Ignores the statements",
        options: [
            "Shows a warning",
            "Prompts to complete the statement",
            "Throws an error",
            "Ignores the statements"],
    },
    {
        number: 5,
        quesTime: 15,
        question: `The "function" and " var" are known as:`,
        answer: "Declaration statements",
        options: ["Keywords", "Data types", "Declaration statements", "Prototypes"],
    },
    {
        number: 6,
        quesTime: 15,
        question: "Which of the following variables takes precedence over the others if the names are the same?",
        answer: "The local element",
        options: [
            "Global variable",
            "The local element",
            "The two of the above",
            "None of the above"],
    },
    {
        number: 7,
        quesTime: 15,
        question: "Which one of the following is the correct way for calling the JavaScript code?",
        answer: "Function/Method",
        options: ["Preprocessor", "Triggering Event", "RMI", "Function/Method"],
    },
    {
        number: 8,
        quesTime: 15,
        question: "Which of the following type of a variable is volatile?",
        answer: "Mutable variable",
        options: ["Mutable variable", "Dynamic variable", "Volatile variable", "Immutable variable"],
    },
    {
        number: 9,
        quesTime: 15,
        question: "When there is an indefinite or an infinite value during an arithmetic computation in a program, then JavaScript prints______.",
        answer: 'Displays "Infinity"',
        options: [
            "Prints an exception error",
            "Prints an overflow error",
            'Displays "Infinity"',
            "Prints the value as such"],
    },
    {
        number: 10,
        quesTime: 15,
        question: "In the JavaScript, which one of the following is not considered as an error:",
        answer: "Division by zero",
        options: ["Syntax error", "Missing of semicolons", "Division by zero", "Missing of Bracket"],
    }
];